<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent Work - Tobias Pörtner on Personal Website of Tobias Pörtner</title>
    <link>http://tobiaspoertner.com/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recent Work - Tobias Pörtner on Personal Website of Tobias Pörtner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobiaspoertner.com/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tobias Pörtner - smartphoniker.de</title>
      <link>http://tobiaspoertner.com/work/smartphoniker-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobiaspoertner.com/work/smartphoniker-de/</guid>
      <description>Design WordPress PHP SEO  smartphoniker.de During my thesis I designed, developed, and deployed a new website for a mobile communications company, which focuses on sustainable solutions for individuals. The website was implemented using custom WordPress functionality as well as a custom-designed theme.
Smartphoniker GmbH is a local mobile communications company from northern Germany, which focuses on sustainable solutions for individuals. Their services include repair of devices, sustainable accessories, mobile phone contracts, and purchasing, refurbishing, and selling used devices to their customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tobias Pörtner - mate</title>
      <link>http://tobiaspoertner.com/work/mate-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobiaspoertner.com/work/mate-app/</guid>
      <description>Flutter Firebase Python Node.js  mate In my final year in university two friends and I created a cross-platform app, which helps students manage their education. The app was developed using Flutter and hooked into a SaaS backend with Firebase Firestore and Google Cloud functions.
Mate was a project two friends and I created as part of classes in university as well as in our spare time. I was responsible for the development, though some tasks were executed by whoever had the knowledge and time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tobias Pörtner - smartphoniker.shop</title>
      <link>http://tobiaspoertner.com/work/smartphoniker-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobiaspoertner.com/work/smartphoniker-shop/</guid>
      <description>Design JavaScript Sass Jinja2  smartphoniker.shop This project is a simple shop system for offering smartphone repairs for a wide range of manufacturers and devices. I was responsible for the design and development of the frontend. The website was implemented using a custom Flask-Server with the Jinja2 Template Engine and a PostgresSQL database.
The client Smartphoniker GmbH is a local mobile communications company based in northern Germany, which focuses on sustainable solutions for individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
